magna.com 2019-03-21

# Privacy

## Privacy Statement

Magna International Inc. (“Magna”) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to preserving your privacy as it relates to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information on this site: [www.magna.com](http://www.magna.com/)

Personal information is information that is personally identifiable to you. Personal information may include your name, email address and mailing address, as the case may be. Visitors to this Web site are not requested to reveal any personal information. However, on a voluntary basis, you may provide and disclose personal information to us in using certain features of our site, such as the Investor Relations section. 

### Registration Forms 

Our Web site has registration forms requiring users to give us contact information. Contact information from these registration forms are used to send users information about our company, provided they have indicated they would like to receive such material. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings using our Update Form or they may opt-out of receiving future email alerts using Email Alerts.

### Information Sharing 

Magna will never disclose, sell or lease to any third party, either free of charge or for remuneration, any personal information that you provide on this site without your permission, unless we are required to do so by law.

### Website Tracking Privacy Principles

In some cases, we collect information about you that is not personal information. Examples of such information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the Web site and/or Internet Service Provider through which you are linked to this site. Such visitor data may be used to improve the content of this Web site and to help us determine which features and services are most important to its visitors. This is done through the use of standard technology called cookies.

### Cookies

Our Web site uses minimal cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to a computer’s hard drive through your browser (if permitted), enabling the site or service provider's system to remember certain information (how many visitors to a site) or preferences, making navigation of a site easier or more user friendly.  These cookies do NOT collect personal data about you, such as name, age, phone number, email address or mailing address. 

If you would prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies. Please note that if you reject or turn cookies off, you will not have access to certain features on our sites that make your online experience more efficient.  

### Links

This site may contain links that take you to other Web sites. This privacy statement does not extend to the data collection practices of third parties and Magna does not assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies or actions of third parties. You should read the individual privacy policies of such sites and make an informed decision as to whether or not you wish to use these sites based on their privacy practices.

### Inquiries

If you submit an email inquiry to this Web site, any personal information you might submit at the same time will only be used by Magna employees or its affiliates who need to have access to it in order to respond to your inquiry. When your personal information is no longer required for the purposes for which it was initially collected or in accordance with other statutory requirements, the information will be destroyed within the next twelve (12) months.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us below.

### Unauthorized Use of information

Magna utilizes various methods to ensure the protection of your personal information. While these methods are considered to be effective, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be lost, used unlawfully or modified in a fraudulent manner since no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely confidential. Consequently, we bear no liability for the use that may be made of the information by you or any third party.

Magna reserves the right to change this privacy statement as it sees fit and without prior notice. However, we will ensure that any change to this statement is in compliance with the laws in effect in Canada with regard to this subject matter and posted on this page.

If you have any comments, questions or concerns regarding Magna's privacy statement or practices, please send your inquiry via email to privacy@magna.com, or in writing at Magna International Inc., 337 Magna Drive Aurora, Ontario, Canada L4G 7K1.

Contact Us with questions about this policy
